[
    {
        "id": "s1",
        "name": "Arvio",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "Greetings! My name is Arvio, but people call me Arvio The Wealthy",
            "Why? I'm the proprietor of MineCroft Coal Mines and the wealthiest coal baron on the seven mountains",
            "My team of Geo ...erm ...geolis ...scientists, say that this town's neighbouring mountains promises bounds of wealth'",
            "I have a proposition for you, allow me to inspect those lands and I may consider helping out this dump *erherm* town"
        ],
        "question": "So what do you say friend? Do we have a deal?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "There's a lot of money in coal. It's a deal!",
                "money": 25,
                "environment": -20,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Arvio brings his crew and begins inspecting your land",
                "state": "s2"
            },
            {
                "label": "No deal, mining for coal will ruin the natural landscape!",
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Arvio leaves with a mischievous look on his face",
                "state": "s2a"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s2",
        "name": "Hunter Gatberg",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "[Ring Ring... Ring Ring...]",
            "Hey Mum! We learnt about polar bears today, they look so cool. I would love to be able to see them one day."
        ],
        "question": "Could you take me on a trip someday?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Of course, my dear",
                "state": "s3"
            },
            {
                "label": "Maybe... I'm busy, Hunter",
                "state": "s3"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s2a",
        "name": "Hunter Gatberg",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "[Ring Ring... Ring Ring...]",
            "Hey Mum! We learnt about polar bears today, they look so cute. I would love to be able to see them one day."
        ],
        "question": "Could you take me on a trip someday?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Of course, my dear",
                "state": "s3a"
            },
            {
                "label": "Maybe... I'm busy, Hunter",
                "state": "s3a"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s3",
        "name": "Arvio",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "Mrs. Gatberg, our prediction was right. Your land is rich with coal."
        ],
        "question": "Will you let us set up an coal mine? We'll pay you.",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Yes",
                "hasAnimation": true,
                "buildingName": "CoalMine",
                "money": 20,
                "environment": -20,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Arvio begins constructing an coal mine. We're getting paid a great amount of money, but this is releasing a lot of CO2.",
                "state": "s4"
            },
            {
                "label": "No, go away Arvio.",
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Arvio leaves you alone",
                "state": "s5"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s3a",
        "name": "Arvio",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "Arvio is sneaky and he has inspected the land without your consent",
            "but he has found that your land is rich with coal, and wishes for your permission to setup a coal mine"
        ],
        "question": "Will you let us set up? We'll pay you.",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Yes",
                "hasAnimation": true,
                "buildingName": "CoalMine",
                "money": 20,
                "happiness": -10,
                "environment": -20,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Arvio begins constructing an coal mine. We're getting paid a great amount of money, but this is releasing a lot of CO2.",
                "state": "s4"
            },
            {
                "label": "No",
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Arvio leaves you alone",
                "state": "s5"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s4",
        "name": "Cowboy Willy",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "A drought is affecting the farmlands of your town, this is affecting all of our local farmers",
            "If this continues we might not be able to grow enough crops for the town",
            "We need as much water as possible, you could pass a temporary law to restrict citizens' water usage to help. "
        ],
        "question": "Will you restrict the town's water usage?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Yes",
                "happiness": -10,
                "environment": 10,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Cowboy Willy is happy with your decision. The townspeople are slightly upset.",
                "state": "s6"
            },
            {
                "label": "No",
                "money": -15,
                "happiness": 5,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "The townspeople did not have to restrict water usage, but you had to import some crops from nearby towns",
                "state": "s7"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s5",
        "name": "Cowboy Willy",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "A drought is affecting the farmlands of your town, this is affecting all of our local farmers",
            "If this continues we might not be able to grow enough crops for the town",
            "We need as much water as possible, you could pass a temporary law to restrict citizens' water usage to help. "
        ],
        "question": "Will you restrict the town's water usage?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Yes",
                "happiness": -10,
                "environment": 10,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "Cowboy Willy is happy with your decision. The townspeople are slightly upset.",
                "state": "s6"
            },
            {
                "label": "No",
                "money": -15,
                "happiness": 5,
                "npcName": "Advisory Board",
                "feedback": "The townspeople did not have to restrict water usage, but you had to import some crops from nearby towns",
                "state": "s7"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s6",
        "name": "Hunter Gatberg",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "Mum, I want a treehouse",
            "All my friends have one..."
        ],
        "question": "Can we build a treehouse?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Yes",
                "state": "s8"
            },
            {
                "label": "No",
                "state": "s9,"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s7",
        "name": "Hunter Gatberg",
        "precedingDialogue": [
            "Mum, I want a treehouse",
            "All my friends have one..."
        ],
        "question": "Can we build a treehouse?",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Yes",
                "state": "s8"
            },
            {
                "label": "No",
                "state": "s9,"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s8",
        "precedingDialogue": [],
        "question": "Your town has grown!",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Continue",
                "feedback": "You have passed level 1"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "s9",
        "precedingDialogue": [],
        "question": "Your town has grown!",
        "transitions": [
            {
                "label": "Continue",
                "feedback": "You have passed level 1"
            }
        ]
    }
]
